And then Juninho beauty Caio goes there with the weeping there mine left me talking
yesterday then brother goes there with the weeping there,
excuse me.
And today is sixty-two.
When I came to this abandoned shed I was washing
it looking I said rascal caraca.
That makes a good deal here,
doesn't it?
But before I reveal what the idea is and what will happen in the coming days.
I need to invest in some things to make the
business more attractive come with me.
Oh,
Juninho has money in his hand,
right?
Then he was touching on the money,
he put his hand on his eye,
he scratched his eye,
then I said O Juninho to stop doing that,
brother.
You're messing with money,
the money is yours.
You put your hand in your eye will get conjunctivitis you said get tested
to leave reserved.
It is a full payment or a thirty percent down payment with
the amount to be agreed up to two days before the event.
The entrepreneur's life is this brother.
Either we take risks and go upstairs and believe
in your ideas or we stay there.
Or waiting for better days.
Man now let's pray for the stop to give some bro my God,
man there Caião.
What you're getting ready calm Cara comes along and sees tio poxa life
you don't like by surprise and we're with her man we're going.